const GENERAL = [
	"What is the worst fashion decision you ever made?",
	"If you had to eat one meal for the rest of your life what would it be?",
	"If you could change gender for a day what’s the first thing you would do?",
	"What’s your biggest irrational phobia and why?",
	"If you became president today, what’s the first bill you would pass?",
	"If you could have any superpower what would it be?",
	"Who was your first celebrity crush?",
	"If you could be somebody else for a day who would you be?",
	"If you were a wrestler what would your entrance theme be?",
	"If aliens landed on earth today and offered to abduct you, would you go with them?",
	"If you could time travel, where is the first place you would go?",
	"If you could live in any historical period, which one would you choose?",
	"If you could be reincarnated as any animal, which one would you choose?",
	"Which famous actor would play you in the movie of your life?",
	"Which famous person, dead or alive, would like by your side during a zombie apocalypse?",
	"What is the worst date you’ve ever been on and why?",
	"What’s a common phrase used in your family that nobody else uses?",
	"What are your most commonly used emojis?",
	"If you could teleport anywhere in the world right now, where would you go?",
	"If you could appear on any game show, which one would you choose?" 
];

const ADULTS = [
	"What do you feel is the secret to a long and happy marriage?" ,
	"What are your biggest fears and biggest excitements about our relationship going forward?" ,
	"Do you feel more emotionally connected than we did early in our relationship?" ,
	"For a happy marriage, do you have to set boundaries?",
	"Is there anything that we used to do before we were married that you miss doing now?" ,
	"What were your first impressions when you met me?" ,
	"What have you learned to appreciate about me that you did not know when we were first married?",
	"Do you think infidelity is always a deal breaker, no matter what?" ,
	"If you had three wishes to wish for our future, what would they be?" ,
	"If you could change one thing about our relationship what would it be?" ,
	"What was the most embarrassing thing to happen at your bachelorette/bachelor party?" ,
	"What’s something you used to believe about relationships, but no longer do?" ,
	"Do you think we manage to balance home and work life well?" ,
	"Do you think we argue more or less than other married couples?" ,
	"What did your family think of me when we first met?",
	"If I loved a name for a child but you hated it, would you let me call our child that?",
	"What do you feel is the secret to a long and happy marriage?" ,
	"What are your biggest fears and biggest excitements about our relationship going forward?",
	"Do you have a naughty fantasy you’ve never shared with me before?",
	"Do you think social media has impacted our relationship since we’ve been married?" ,
	"Did your family or friends find the best man’s speech offensive?" ,
	"Is there anything you’ve always wondered about me, but have hesitated to ask" ,
	"What do you think is the biggest cause of or contributing factor towards divorce?" ,
	"If you could go back, would you have done anything differently about the wedding?" ,
	"If you could go back, would you have moved abroad to start our life together?",
	"What have we learned most about each other since being together?" ,
	"What was the most fun thing we did on our honeymoon?",
	"Which of our marriage vows do you think is the most important?" ,
	"What has been the best anniversary gift you’ve gotten me?" ,
	"What do you think would be the most romantic place for us to travel together?" ,
	"What has been the most romantic thing you’ve done for me?" ,
	"When we got married, how did we decide where we wanted to live?" ,
	"Looking back now, was there a situation you wished you’d handled differently?" ,
	"Do we still make time for each other now as we did at the start?" ,
	"What annoying habits do I have?" ,
	"Did anything funny happen at the wedding?" ,
	"What are some situations we’ve been through that have made us stronger as people?" ,
	"What’s one thing I do around the house that annoys you?" ,
	"What world events have had an impact on our marriage?" ,
	"When did you realize I was the one?" ,
	"Do you prefer sitting under the stars or watching a sunset?" ,
	"What helps you de-stress?" ,
	"What strengths do we both bring to the relationship?" ,
	"Do you think we’re closer now than we were at the beginning of the relationship?" ,
	"Do you think our star signs have helped us to be a closer couple?",
	"When you think of our home, what’s the first thing that comes to mind?" ,
	"What’s the best advice someone has ever given you?" ,
	"What’s your most significant achievement?" ,
	"If you could bring a previous pet back from the dead, who would you pick?" ,
	"If you could sum up our relationship in 3 words, what would it be?" ,
	"Do you think our kids are or will be more like you or more like me?" ,
	"If you could pick any other era to live in, which would you choose and why?" ,
	"Do you believe in life after death?" ,
	"What’s one thing you’ve done that other people would never know?" ,
	"What’s the best gift you’ve ever received?",
	"Do you think we will all live on a different planet one day, or can we save this one?" ,
	"Do you think humans were created or evolved from apes?" ,
	"What’s a regret you have about your life so far?",
	"What moment changed your life for good?" ,
	"If you could change one thing about yourself, what would it be and why?" ,
	"Rank your three happiest days so far?",
	"At what moment in your life so far have you felt most alive?" ,
	"Have you ever really fallen out with a close friend?" ,
	"Before you met me, were you heartbroken?",
	"Do you think there is any such thing as pure happiness? Have you ever experienced it in life?" ,
	"What’s the most trouble you’ve ever been in?" ,
	"What legacy would you like to leave in this world?" ,
	"Do you think you have a purpose in life? If so, what is it?" ,
	"What does true love look like to you?" ,
	"What do you think our love language is?" ,
	"Are you proud of me?" ,
	"How can I show you more love and affection?" ,
	"What can we do to improve our relationship?" ,
	"In what ways can we make our finances better?" ,
	"What’s going on in your head right now?" ,
	"What can you tell me that will give me insight into what you’re thinking?" ,
	"Which romantic film best relates to us?" ,
	"If someone wrote a book about our relationship, would it be a romantic comedy or emotionally profound?" ,
	"If someone gave you a letter letting you know how our relationship will look in 10 years, would you read it?" ,
	"What can I do to make you feel more secure?" ,
	"Would you like me to give you more surprises in life?" ,
	"If you could only eat one of my meals for the rest of your life, what would it be and why?" ,
	"Would you like to go on more date nights?" ,
	"Would a new challenge help us grow as people?" ,
	"Do I tell you enough about how much you mean to me?" ,
	"Which movie, no matter how many times you watch it, always makes you cry?" ,
	"Do you remember the story of how we met?" ,
	"Which couple out of your friends or family do you envy the most?" ,
	"Tell me about your first love?" ,
	"What would have been a relationship deal breaker for you when we first met?" ,
	"What can we do to be more intimate with each other?" ,
	"What would be the perfect end to a date with me?" ,
	"What’s the worst chat-up line you used when dating?" ,
	"What was the most embarrassing thing you did to get the attention of a girl/boy?" ,
	"What memory of me always sticks in your head?" ,
	"What part of my body can you not get enough of?" ,
	"Is there anything new you would like to try in bed? If so, what is it?" ,
	"Would you like us to have more foreplay?" ,
	"What could I wear that would get you in the mood?" ,
	"What always makes you happy when you’re sad?" ,
	"Before we got together, what was your type?" ,
	"What does romance mean to you?" ,
	"Have you ever been tempted to end our relationship?" ,
	"Would you tell me if you had feelings for somebody else?" ,
	"What’s the most romantic thing you’ve ever seen?" ,
	"What song always reminds me of you?" ,
	"At what age did you have the dreaded birds and the bees talk?" ,
	"What romantic getaway would you like to try next?" ,
	"Do you think we’re soulmates? Do you think soulmates exist?" ,
	"Have you ever been jealous of something I have?" ,
 	"What’s your greatest dream, and did it come true?" 

];


const bible_questions = [
	"Q1: How many commandments are there in the Bible?",
	"Q2: What is the first book in the new testament?",
	"Q3: What is the first book in the old testament?",
	"Q4: What did God do on the 7th day?",
	"Q5: Who built an ark?",
	"Q6: Who is the mother of Jesus?",
	"Q7: What are the first three words in Genesis?",
	"Q8: What is the shortest verse in the bible?",
	"Q9: What is the longest chapter in the bible?",
	"Q10: What is the middle chapter in the bible?",
	"Q11: What is the longest verse in the bible?",
	"Q12: How many sons did Jacob have?",
	"Q13: How old was Abraham when Isaac was born?",
	"Q14: How old was Sarah when Isaac was born?",
	"Q15: Who was older Ishmael or Isaac?",
	"Q16: What is the meaning of the name Isaac in the bible?",
	"Q17: Where was Jesus buried?",
	"Q18: How many days was Jesus in the tomb?",
	"Q19: What is the shortest book in the new testament?",
	"Q20: How many days was Jonah in the belly of the big fish?",
	"Q21: Who wrote the Book of Revelation?",
	"Q22: What does the word 'gospel' mean?",
	"Q23: How many disciples did Jesus have?",
	"Q24: How many times did Peter deny Jesus?",
	"Q25: What is another name for the Sermon on the Mount?",
	"Q26: Where was Moses born in the Bible?",
	"Q27: How many plagues of Egypt are there in the bible?",
	"Q28: What were the 10 plagues of Egypt?",
	"Q29: Who killed Goliath?",
	"Q30: Who threw Daniel in the lion’s den?",
	"Q31: Who threw Shadrach Meshach and Abednego in the fire?",
	"Q32: Who was the Pharisee that had a private meeting with Jesus at night?",
	"Q33: Which chapter of Hebrews tells of great heroes of faith?",
	"Q34: Which book in the Bible tells of Paul’s conversion?",
	"Q35: Prophet Isaiah lived in which city?",
	"Q36: Ahab was the king of which country?",
	"Q37: Finish this sentence: We are not saved by our own works, we are saved by _?",
	"Q38: What did David use to kill Goliath?",
	"Q39: What did the bread and wine Jesus served the disciples at the Last Supper represent?",
	"Q40: Even though he promised Jesus he would die for him, what did Peter do when Jesus was arrested?",
	"Q41: What was the name of the demon who possessed the man in the tomb?",
	"Q42: What happened to Joseph after he had refused to commit adultery with his master's wife?",
	"Q43: What is the name given to an unusual happening that goes against the laws of nature?",
	"Q44: What is the meaning of 'Epistle'?",
	"Q45: Jesus said what is the greatest display of love?",
	"Q46: Which Queen visited King Solomon because she had heard of his fame?",
	"Q47: True or False, the word 'Easter' appears in the Old Testament?",
	"Q49: Who is the man that wanted to kill baby Jesus?",
	"Q50: How many books of poetry are in the Old Testament?",
	"Q51: Ten men with what condition were healed by Jesus?",
	"Q52: In the book of Genesis, God did what to Adam and Eve when he found that they had sinned?",
	"Q53: What was the animal Satan appeared as to Eve in the book of Genesis?",
	"Q54: Which book tells of seven seals and seven trumpets?",
	"Q55: What is Pentecost?" ,
	"Q56: What is the sacrament in which we first become children of God?",
	"Q57: Who was the boy who killed the Philistine giant?",
	"Q58: What does 'Eve' mean?",
	"Q59: Why is Easter celebrated?",
	"Q60: Which prophet had to lay on his left side for six months?",
	"Q61: How old was Abraham in the bible when he died?",
	"Q62: How old was Jesus when he was crucified?",
	"Q63: What is the shortest book in the old testament?",
	"Q64: How old was Jesus when he returned from Egypt?",
	"Q65: Who married Boaz in the bible?",
	"Q66: How old was Joseph when he married Mary in the bible?",
	"Q67: Who married Rebecca in the bible?",
	"Q68: Who had the most wives in the Bible?",
	"Q69: Where did Cain's wife come from in the Bible?",
	"Q70: What was Lot's wife name in the Bible?"

	
]







const bible_answers = [
	{Question:	"Q1",	answer:	 "10"},
	{Question:	"Q2",	answer:	 "Matthew"},
	{Question:	"Q3",	answer:	 "Genesis"},
	{Question:	"Q4",	answer:	 "He rested"},
	{Question:	"Q5",	answer:	 "Noah"},
	{Question:	"Q6",	answer:	 "Mary"},
	{Question:	"Q7",	answer:	 "In the beginning"},
	{Question:	"Q8",	answer:	 "Jesus wept"},
	{Question:	"Q9",	answer:	 "Psalm 119"},
	{Question:	"Q10",	answer:	 "Psalm 117"},
	{Question:	"Q11",	answer:	 "Esther 8:9"},
	{Question:	"Q12",	answer:	 "12"},
	{Question:	"Q13",	answer:	 "100"},
	{Question:	"Q14",	answer:	 "90"},
	{Question:	"Q15",	answer:	 "Ishmael"},
	{Question:	"Q16",	answer:	 "One who laughs"},
	{Question:	"Q17",	answer:	 "In a tomb"},
	{Question:	"Q18",	answer:	 "3 days"},
	{Question:	"Q19",	answer:	 "2 John"},
	{Question:	"Q20",	answer:	 "3 days and 3 nights"},
	{Question:	"Q21",	answer:	 "Apostle John"},
	{Question:	"Q22",	answer:	 "Good News"},
	{Question:	"Q23",	answer:	 "12"},
	{Question:	"Q24",	answer:	 "3 times"},
	{Question:	"Q25",	answer:	 "The Beatitudes"},
	{Question:	"Q26",	answer:	 "Goshen in ancient Egypt"},
	{Question:	"Q27",	answer:	 "10"},
	{Question:	"Q28",	answer:	 "Water turning to blood; Frogs, Lice, Flies, Livestock pestilence, Boils, Hail, Locusts, Darkness and the Killing of firstborn children"},
	{Question:	"Q29",	answer:	 "David"},
	{Question:	"Q30",	answer:	 "King Darius"},
	{Question:	"Q31",	answer:	 "Nebuchadnezzar, King of Babylon"},
	{Question:	"Q32",	answer:	 "Nicodemus"},
	{Question:	"Q33",	answer:	 "Hebrews 11"},
	{Question:	"Q34",	answer:	 "Acts"},
	{Question:	"Q35",	answer:	 "Jerusalem"},
	{Question:	"Q36",	answer:	 "Israel"},
	{Question:	"Q37",	answer:	 "Grace"},
	{Question:	"Q38",	answer:	 "A sling and a stone"},
	{Question:	"Q39",	answer:	 "Body & Blood, Soul & Divinity of Jesus Christ"},
	{Question:	"Q40",	answer:	 "Peter denied that he knew Jesus three times"},
	{Question:	"Q41",	answer:	 "Legion"},
	{Question:	"Q42",	answer:	 "He was put in jail"},
	{Question:	"Q43",	answer:	 "Miracles"},
	{Question:	"Q44",	answer:	 "Letter"},
	{Question:	"Q45",	answer:	 "That a man would lay down his life for a friend"},
	{Question:  "Q46",  answer:  "The Queen of Sheba."},
	{Question:	"Q47",	answer:	 "False"},
	{Question:	"Q49",	answer:	 "King Herod"},
	{Question:	"Q50",	answer:	 "Five"},
	{Question:	"Q51",	answer:	 "Leoprasy"},
	{Question:	"Q52",	answer:	 "He expelled them from the garden of Eden"},
	{Question:	"Q53",	answer:	 "Serpent"},
	{Question:	"Q54",	answer:	 "Revelation"},
	{Question:	"Q55",	answer:	 "When the Holy Spirit descended onto the apostles in flaming fire to give them the gifts to courageously proclaim the good news of Jesus"},
	{Question:	"Q56",	answer:	 "Baptism"},
	{Question:	"Q57",	answer:	 "David"},
	{Question:	"Q58",	answer:	 "Mother of all living"},
	{Question:	"Q59",	answer:	 "It is the day of Jesus Christ's Resurrection"},
	{Question:	"Q60",	answer:	 "Ezekiel"},
	{Question:	"Q61",	answer:	 "175 (Genesis 25:7)"},
	{Question:	"Q62",	answer:	 "No one knows as it was not recorded in the Bible"},
	{Question:	"Q63",	answer:	 "Obadiah (21 verses only)"},
	{Question:	"Q64",	answer:	 "The Bible does not say"},
	{Question:	"Q65",	answer:	 "Ruth"},
	{Question:	"Q66",	answer:	 "Not mentioned in the Bible"},
	{Question:	"Q67",	answer:	 "Isaac"},
	{Question:	"Q68",	answer:	 "King Solomon"},
	{Question:	"Q69",	answer:	 "Its not mentioned in the Bible but it is widely believed that Cain married his sister."},
	{Question:	"Q70",	answer:	 "Her name is not mentioned in the Bible."},

		

]

const CHILDREN = [
		"If your stuffed animals could talk, what would they say?",
		"What does it feel like when I hug you?",
		"If you drew everything that came into your head, what would you be drawing right now?",
		"What do you think you're going to dream about tonight?",
		"What sounds do you like best and why?",
		"If you were going to spend the whole day outside, what activities would you do?",
		"What are the best ways to make a fort?",
		"How do you think animals communicate?",
		"Describe a great day: What are you doing that makes it special?",
		"What animal would make a great driver?",
		"Do you like it when other people share with you? Why?",
		"Who is your favorite storybook character?",
		"What one thing do you do now that you usually need an adult for but would like to try to do all by yourself?",
		"If you had to give everyone in the family new names, what would they be?",
		"What makes you happy?",
		"If you could do anything right now, what would you do?",
		"If you had a pet dragon, what would you name it?",
		"What would you do together with your pet dragon?",
		"Do you ever think about renaming the colors of your crayons?",
		"What movie, TV, or book character makes you laugh the most?",
		"If you opened a store, what would you sell?",
		"What's your superhero name, and what powers do you have?",
		"If you could grow anything in the yard, what would it be?",
		"What do you enjoy giving to people?",
		"Did you smile or laugh extra today? What did you laugh about?",
		"Pretend you're a chef and tell me about your restaurant: What foods do you serve?",
		"If you could ask a wild animal any question, what would you ask?",
		"If you were a photographer for a day, what would you take pictures of?",
		"Do you have any inventions in your brain?",
		"If you could make up a new holiday, what would it be?",
		"What would you do if you made the rules at home?",
		"What was your favorite thing about today?",
		"What do you like daydreaming about?",
		"What is something about you that you think I might not know?",
		"What's a memory that makes you happy?",
		"Let's say you're at the beach: What's the first thing you do?",
		"What makes you feel loved?",
		"If you could give $100 to a charity, what charity would you choose?",
		"If you wrote a book, what would it be about?",
		"How do you best like helping others?",
		"If you lived in a cave in the woods, what would be inside it?",
		"If you were in a play, what would your character be like?",
		"What makes you so awesome?",
		"If you had friends all over the world, how would you keep in touch?",
		"If you were a teacher and could teach your students anything at all, what would you teach them?",
		"If a friend asked you to keep a secret that you don't feel comfortable keeping, what would you do?",


]

const Bible_Q_A = [
	{Question: "Q1: How many commandments are there in the Bible?",	Answer:"10"},
	{Question: "Q2: What is the first book in the new testament?",	Answer:"Matthew"},
	{Question: "Q3: What is the first book in the old testament?",	Answer:"Genesis"},
	{Question: "Q4: What did God do on the 7th day?",	Answer:"He rested"},
	{Question: "Q5: Who built an ark?",	Answer:"Noah"},
	{Question: "Q6: Who is the mother of Jesus?",	Answer:"Mary"},
	{Question: "Q7: What are the first three words in Genesis?",	Answer:"In the beginning"},
	{Question: "Q8: What is the shortest verse in the bible?",	Answer:"Jesus wept"},
	{Question: "Q9: What is the longest chapter in the bible?",	Answer:"Psalm 119"},
	{Question: "Q10: What is the middle chapter in the bible?",	Answer:"Psalm 117"},
	{Question: "Q11: What is the longest verse in the bible?",	Answer:"Esther 8:9"},
	{Question: "Q12: How many sons did Jacob have?",	Answer:"12"},
	{Question: "Q13: How old was Abraham when Isaac was born?",	Answer:"100"},
	{Question: "Q14: How old was Sarah when Isaac was born?",	Answer:"90"},
	{Question: "Q15: Who was older Ishmael or Isaac?",	Answer:"Ishmael"},
	{Question: "Q16: What is the meaning of the name Isaac in the bible?",	Answer:"One who laughs"},
	{Question: "Q17: Where was Jesus buried?",	Answer:"In a tomb"},
	{Question: "Q18: How many days was Jesus in the tomb?",	Answer:"3 days"},
	{Question: "Q19: What is the shortest book in the new testament?",	Answer:"2 John"},
	{Question: "Q20: How many days was Jonah in the belly of the big fish?",	Answer:"3 days and 3 nights"},
	{Question: "Q21: Who wrote the Book of Revelation?",	Answer:"Apostle John"},
	{Question: "Q22: What does the word 'gospel' mean?",	Answer:"Good News"},
	{Question: "Q23: How many disciples did Jesus have?",	Answer:"12"},
	{Question: "Q24: How many times did Peter deny Jesus?",	Answer:"3 times"},
	{Question: "Q25: What is another name for the Sermon on the Mount?",	Answer:"The Beatitudes"},
	{Question: "Q26: Where was Moses born in the Bible?",	Answer:"Goshen in ancient Egypt"},
	{Question: "Q27: How many plagues of Egypt are there in the bible?",	Answer:"10"},
	{Question: "Q28: What were the 10 plagues of Egypt?",	Answer:"Water turning to blood; Frogs, Lice, Flies, Livestock pestilence, Boils, Hail, Locusts, Darkness and the Killing of firstborn children"},
	{Question: "Q29: Who killed Goliath?",	Answer:"David"},
	{Question: "Q30: Who threw Daniel in the lion’s den?",	Answer:"King Darius"},
	{Question: "Q31: Who threw Shadrach Meshach and Abednego in the fire?",	Answer:"Nebuchadnezzar, King of Babylon"},
	{Question: "Q32: Who was the Pharisee that had a private meeting with Jesus at night?",	Answer:"Nicodemus"},
	{Question: "Q33: Which chapter of Hebrews tells of great heroes of faith?",	Answer:"Hebrews 11"},
	{Question: "Q34: Which book in the Bible tells of Paul’s conversion?",	Answer:"Acts"},
	{Question: "Q35: Prophet Isaiah lived in which city?",	Answer:"Jerusalem"},
	{Question: "Q36: Ahab was the king of which country?",	Answer:"Israel"},
	{Question: "Q37: Finish this sentence: We are not saved by our own works, we are saved by _?_",	Answer:"Grace"},
	{Question: "Q38: What did David use to kill Goliath?",	Answer:"A sling and a stone"},
	{Question: "Q39: What did the bread and wine Jesus served the disciples at the Last Supper represent?",	Answer:"Body & Blood, Soul & Divinity of Jesus Christ"},
	{Question: "Q40: Even though he promised Jesus he would die for him, what did Peter do when Jesus was arrested?",	Answer:"Peter denied that he knew Jesus three times"},
	{Question: "Q41: What was the name of the demon who possessed the man in the tomb?",	Answer:"Legion"},
	{Question: "Q42: What happened to Joseph after he had refused to commit adultery with his master's wife?",	Answer:"He was put in jail"},
	{Question: "Q43: What is the name given to an unusual happening that goes against the laws of nature?",	Answer:"Miracles"},
	{Question: "Q44: What is the meaning of 'Epistle'?",	Answer:"Letter"},
	{Question: "Q45: Jesus said what is the greatest display of love?",	Answer:"That a man would lay down his life for a friend"},
	{Question: "Q46: Which Queen visited King Solomon because she had heard of his fame?",	Answer:"The Queen of Sheba"},
	{Question: "Q47: True or False, the word 'Easter' appears in the Old Testament?",	Answer:"False"},
	{Question: "Q48: The Easter sunrise service, a distinctive Protestant observance in North America, comes from what Biblical event?",	Answer:"A reenactment of Mary Magdalene’s visit to Jesus’ tomb on the morning of his Resurrection"},
	{Question: "Q49: Who is the man that wanted to kill baby Jesus?",	Answer:"King Herod"},
	{Question: "Q50: How many books of poetry are in the Old Testament?",	Answer:"Five"},
	{Question: "Q51: Ten men with what condition were healed by Jesus?",	Answer:"Leoprasy"},
	{Question: "Q52: In the book of Genesis, God did what to Adam and Eve when he found that they had sinned?",	Answer:"He expelled them from the garden of Eden"},
	{Question: "Q53: What was the animal Satan appeared as to Eve in the book of Genesis?",	Answer:"Serpent"},
	{Question: "Q54: Which book tells of seven seals and seven trumpets?",	Answer:"Revelation"},
	{Question: "Q55: What is Pentecost?",	Answer:"When the Holy Spirit descended onto the apostles in flaming fire to give them the gifts to courageously proclaim the good news of Jesus"},
	{Question: "Q56: What is the sacrament in which we first become children of God?",	Answer:"Baptism"},
	{Question: "Q57: Who was the boy who killed the Philistine giant?",	Answer:"David"},
	{Question: "Q58: What does 'Eve' mean?",	Answer:"Mother of all living"},
	{Question: "Q59: Why is Easter celebrated?",	Answer:"It is the day of Jesus Christ's Resurrection"},
	{Question: "Q60: Which prophet had to lay on his left side for six months?",	Answer:"Ezekiel"},
	{Question: "Q61: How old was Abraham in the bible when he died?",	Answer:"175 (Genesis 25:7)"},
	{Question: "Q62: How old was Jesus when he was crucified?",	Answer:"No one knows as it was not recorded in the Bible"},
	{Question: "Q63: The shortest book in the old testament is?",	Answer:"Obadiah (21 verses only)"},
	{Question: "Q64: How old was Jesus when he returned from Egypt?",	Answer:"The Bible does not say"},
	{Question: "Q65: Who married Boaz in the bible?",	Answer:"Ruth"},
	{Question: "Q66: How old was Joseph when he married Mary in the bible?",	Answer:"Not mentioned in the Bible"},
	{Question: "Q67: Who married Rebecca in the bible?",	Answer:"Isaac"},
	{Question: "Q68: Who had the most wives in the Bible?",	Answer:"King Solomon"},
	{Question: "Q69: Where did Cain's wife come from in the Bible?",	Answer:"Its not mentioned in the Bible but it is widely believed that Cain married his sister"},
	{Question: "Q70: What was Lot's wife name in the Bible?",	Answer:"Her name is not mentioned in the Bible"}

];

const Fun_General = [
	{Question: "Q1 How many legs does a spider have?", Answer: "Eight"},
	{Question: "Q2 What is the name of the toy cowboy in Toy Story?", Answer: "Woody"},
	{Question: "Q3 What is the color of an emerald?", Answer: "Green"},
	{Question: "Q4 What is something you hit with a hammer?", Answer: "A nail"},
	{Question: "Q5 What's the name of a place you go to see lots of animals?", Answer: "The zoo"},
	{Question: "Q6 Whose nose grew longer every time he lied?", Answer: "Pinocchio"},
	{Question: "Q7 What is the name of the fairy in Peter Pan?", Answer: "Tinkerbell"},
	{Question: "Q8 If you freeze water, what do you get?", Answer: "Ice"},
	{Question: "Q9 What colors are the stars on the American flag?", Answer: "White"},
	{Question: "Q10 In the nursery rhyme, Jack and Jill, what do Jack and Jill go up the hill to fetch?", Answer: "A pail of water"},
	{Question: "Q11 Where does the President of the United States live while in office?", Answer: "The White House"},
	{Question: "Q12 How many planets are in our solar system?", Answer: "Eight"},
	{Question: "Q13 Which ocean is off the California coast?", Answer: "The Pacific"},
	{Question: "Q14 What fruit do kids traditionally give to teachers?", Answer: "An apple"},
	{Question: "Q15 What's the response to 'see you later, alligator?' ", Answer: "'In a while, crocodile.'"},
	{Question: "Q16 Which Disney movie is Elsa in?", Answer: "Frozen"},
	{Question: "Q17 Who is Mickey Mouse's girlfriend?", Answer: "Minnie Mouse"},
	{Question: "Q18 Where does Santa Claus live?", Answer: "The North Pole"},
	{Question: "Q19 According to the Dr. Seuss book, who stole Christmas?", Answer: "The Grinch"},
	{Question: "Q20 Which state is famous for Hollywood?", Answer: "California"},
	{Question: "Q21 What type of fish is Nemo?", Answer: "A clownfish"},
	{Question: "Q22 What do caterpillars turn into?", Answer: "Butterflies"},
	{Question: "Q23 What is the color of a school bus?", Answer: "Yellow"},
	{Question: "Q24 What do you use to write on a blackboard?", Answer: "Chalk"},
	{Question: "Q25 On which holiday do you go trick-or-treating?", Answer: "Halloween"},
	{Question: "Q26 How many pairs of wings do bees have?", Answer: "Two"},
	{Question: "Q27 Where is the Great Pyramid of Giza?", Answer: "Egypt"},
	{Question: "Q28 What is a doe?", Answer: "A female deer"},
	{Question: "Q29 What do bees make?", Answer: "Honey"},
	{Question: "Q30 When do leaves die?", Answer: "In the fall"},
	{Question: "Q31 What kind of cat is considered bad luck?", Answer: "Black cats"},
	{Question: "Q32 How many days are in a year?", Answer: "365"},
	{Question: "Q33 What is the name of the pirate in Peter Pan?", Answer: "Captain Hook"},
	{Question: "Q34 What is a brontosaurus?", Answer: "A dinosaur"},
	{Question: "Q35 What is a group of lions called?", Answer: "A pride"},
	{Question: "Q36 Which is the fastest land animal?", Answer: "The cheetah"},
	{Question: "Q37 What kind of animal was Abu in Aladdin?", Answer: "A monkey"},
	{Question: "Q38 Who wrote Hamlet?", Answer: "William Shakespeare"},
	{Question: "Q39 Who built the pyramids?", Answer: "The Egyptians"},
	{Question: "Q40 In the nursery rhyme, who sat on a wall before having a great fall?", Answer: "Humpty Dumpty"},
	{Question: "Q41 On the farm, what is a kid?", Answer: "A baby goat"},
	{Question: "Q42 What is the name of Harry Potter's pet owl?", Answer: "Hedwig"},
	{Question: "Q43 What color are Smurfs?", Answer: "Blue"},
	{Question: "Q44 Name Batman’s crime-fighting partner?", Answer: "Robin"},
	{Question: "Q45 How many sides does a triangle have?", Answer: "Three"},
	{Question: "Q46 Which superhero can climb up walls and buildings?", Answer: "Spiderman"},
	{Question: "Q47 'Stars and Stripes' is the nickname of the flag of which country?", Answer: "United States of America"},
	{Question: "Q48 Which planet in our Solar System is known for having a ring?", Answer: "Saturn"},
	{Question: "Q49 Why do things fall when you drop them?", Answer: "Because of gravity"},
	{Question: "Q50 What is the largest mammal in the world?", Answer: "A whale"},
	{Question: "Q51 How many colors are in a rainbow?", Answer: "Seven"},
	{Question: "Q52 Who is the patron saint of Ireland?", Answer: "St. Patrick"},
	{Question: "Q53 In which capital city of Europe would you find the Eiffel Tower?", Answer: "Paris"},
	{Question: "Q54 What do you have to stick on an envelope?", Answer: "A stamp"},
	{Question: "Q55 Who was the first American president?", Answer: "George Washington"},
	{Question: "Q56 Which country is home to the kangaroo?", Answer: "Australia"},
	{Question: "Q57 What is the opposite of ‘cheap’?", Answer: "Expensive"},
	{Question: "Q58 Which animal is the tallest in the world?", Answer: "Giraffe"},
	{Question: "Q59 Which singing voice is the highest pitch? Soprano, tenor or baritone?", Answer: "Soprano"},
	{Question: "Q60 A scientist who studies rocks is called a what?", Answer: "A geologist"},
	{Question: "Q61 Who was the first man to step on the moon?", Answer: "Neil Armstrong"},
	{Question: "Q62 What could make Harry Potter invisible?", Answer: "The Invisibility Cloak"},
	{Question: "Q63 In sports, what is an MVP?", Answer: "Most Valuable Player"},
	{Question: "Q64 If you suffer from arachnophobia, which animal are you scared of?", Answer: "Spiders"},
	{Question: "Q65 What's the response to 'see you later, alligator?' ", Answer: "In a while, crocodile."},
	{Question: "Q66 What food do pandas eat?", Answer: "Bamboo"},
	{Question: "Q67 Which place is called 'the happiest place in the world?'", Answer: "Disney World"},
	{Question: "Q68 What day of the year is Independence Day?", Answer: "July 4th"},
	{Question: "Q69 How many continents are there in the world?", Answer: "Seven"},
	{Question: "Q70 What is the largest state in America?", Answer: "Alaska"},
	{Question: "Q71 What is the smallest state in America?", Answer: "Rhode Island"},
	{Question: "Q72 Two of the planets in our solar system begin with the letter M, can you name them?", Answer: "Mars and Mercury"},
	{Question: "Q73 What kind of tree do acorns come from?", Answer: "Oak"},
	{Question: "Q74 How many bones do sharks have?", Answer: "Zero"},
	{Question: "Q75 What is the name of molten rock after a volcanic eruption?", Answer: "Lava"},
	{Question: "Q76 What is the part of the human eye that controls the amount of light that passes through the pupil?", Answer: "The iris"},
	{Question: "Q77 Can you name the closest star to Earth?", Answer: "The sun"},
	{Question: "Q78 What was the last name of the flying pioneers Orville and Wilbur?", Answer: "Wright"},
	{Question: "Q79 Can you name the seven dwarves in Snow White?", Answer: "Sleepy, Sneezy, Happy, Grumpy, Dopey, Doc, and Bashful"},
	{Question: "Q80 In what country were the Olympic Games invented?", Answer: "Greece"},
	{Question: "Q81 Who was the 16th president of the United States?", Answer: "Abraham Lincoln"},
	{Question: "Q82 Who invented the telephone?", Answer: "Alexander Graham Bell"},
	{Question: "Q83 The Statue of Liberty came from which country to the United States?", Answer: "France"},
	{Question: "Q84 Who painted the Mona Lisa?", Answer: "Leonardo DaVinci"},
	{Question: "Q85 What’s the name of the town where The Flintstones live?", Answer: "Bedrock"},
	{Question: "Q86 Which famous ocean liner sank on her first voyage in 1912?", Answer: "The Titanic"},
	{Question: "Q87 Which movie is Prince Charming from?", Answer: "Cinderella"},
	{Question: "Q88 Which country did Justin Bieber come from?", Answer: "Canada"},
	{Question: "Q89 What is the nickname for the bell of the clock at the Palace of Westminster in London?", Answer: "Big Ben"},
	{Question: "Q90 What do you get when you boil water?", Answer: "Steam"},
	{Question: "Q91 What is the name of Mickey Mouse's pet dog?", Answer: "Pluto"},
	{Question: "Q92 In what movie will you find characters who are looking for a brain, a heart, and courage?", Answer: "The Wizard of Oz"},
	{Question: "Q93 What movie is Princess Fiona from?", Answer: "Shrek"},
	{Question: "Q94 What is the largest continent?", Answer: "Asia"},
	{Question: "Q95 What is the tallest mountain in the world?", Answer: "Mount Everest"},
	{Question: "Q96 How many Great Lakes are there?", Answer: "Five"},
	{Question: "Q97 What is the imaginary line called that connects the North and South Pole?", Answer: "Prime Meridian"},
	{Question: "Q98 What kind of tree do prunes come from?", Answer: "A plum tree"},
	{Question: "Q99 What gulf is located to the south of Florida?", Answer: "The Gulf of Mexico"},
	{Question: "Q100 What is the hardest natural substance?", Answer: "A diamond"},
	{Question: "Q101 Which state was the 50th state to join the union?", Answer: "Hawaii"},

	
]


const NewBible=[
{Question: "Q1: True or False: The Bible is the most popular book ever written. (by copies sold)",	Answer: " True."},
{Question: "Q2: What is the first book in the Bible?",	Answer: " Genesis"},
{Question: "Q3: How many days did God take to create the world?",	Answer: " 6"},
{Question: "Q4: Who was the first man?",	Answer: " Adam"},
{Question: "Q5: Who was the first woman?",	Answer: " Eve"},
{Question: "Q6: Where did Adam and Eve live at the beginning of the world?",	Answer: " Garden of Eden"},
{Question: "Q7: Who were their three sons listed in the Bible?",	Answer: " Cain, Abel, Seth"},
{Question: "Q8: Who did God tell to build an ark?",	Answer: " Noah"},
{Question: "Q9: How many days and nights did it rain when Noah was on the ark?",	Answer: " 40"},
{Question: "Q10: What was God’s sign to Noah that he would never destroy the earth again?",	Answer: " A rainbow"},
{Question: "Q11: How many brothers did Joseph have?",	Answer: " 11"},
{Question: "Q12: What did Joseph tell his brothers about his dreams that upset them?",	Answer: " The dreams said he would become greater and rule over them."},
{Question: "Q13: How did Moses’ mother save him from the Egyptian soldiers?",	Answer: " Put him in a basket in the river."},
{Question: "Q14: Through what did God speak to Moses in the desert?",	Answer: " A burning bush."},
{Question: "Q15: What did Moses say God commanded the Pharaoh to do?",	Answer: " Let his people go."},
{Question: "Q16: How many plagues did God send on Egypt?",	Answer: " 10"},
{Question: "Q17: What was the final plague that convinced Pharaoh to let the slaves go?",	Answer: "  The firstborn son of all Egyptian families died."},
{Question: "Q18: When Pharaoh changed his mind and sent his army after the slaves, where did they meet at?",	Answer: " By the Red Sea"},
{Question: "Q19: What did God through Moses to save the slaves?",	Answer: " Parted the Red Sea."},
{Question: "Q20: When the Egyptians tried to follow the Israelites through the Red Sea, what happened?",	Answer: " The water crashed on them and killed them all."},
{Question: "Q21: Where did God give Moses the Ten Commandments?",	Answer: " Mt. Sinai"},
{Question: "Q22: What golden image did the Israelites make at Mt. Sinai?",	Answer: " A golden calf"},
{Question: "Q23: Who was the first king of Israel?",	Answer: " Saul"},
{Question: "Q24: When Daniel prayed to God after it was not allowed, where was he thrown into?",	Answer: " The lion’s den"},
{Question: "Q25: Who was Jesus' human mother?",	Answer: " Mary"},
{Question: "Q26: Who was Jesus’ adoptive father on Earth?",	Answer: " Joseph"},
{Question: "Q27: Who was Jesus’ birth father?",	Answer: " God"},
{Question: "Q28: Name the city where Jesus was born.",	Answer: " Bethlehem"},
{Question: "Q29: True or False: Because Jesus was God, he didn’t obey his parents’ rules.",	Answer: " False. Jesus obeyed his parents."},
{Question: "Q30: Who baptized Jesus?",	Answer: " John the Baptist"},
{Question: "Q31: Who spoke from the sky when Jesus was baptized?",	Answer: " God"},
{Question: "Q32: What did God say?",	Answer: " That he was pleased with his son."},
{Question: "Q33: Before Jesus started preaching, what was his job?",	Answer: " Carpenter"},
{Question: "Q34: Name Jesus’ hometown",	Answer: " Nazareth"},
{Question: "Q35:  True or False: Jesus turned water into Pepsi.",	Answer: " False, Jesus turned water into wine."},
{Question: "Q36: Name the place where Jesus walked on water?",	Answer: " Sea of Galilee"},
{Question: "Q37: True or False: Jesus stayed away from people with bad reputations?",	Answer: " False. He often ate with “sinners.”"},
{Question: "Q38: True or False: Everywhere he went, people loved Jesus and believed his message?",	Answer: " False. Jesus was rejected many times."},
{Question: "Q39: How many disciples did Jesus choose?",	Answer: " 12"},
{Question: "Q40: Besides preaching, name an activity Jesus did while traveling in Galilee",	Answer: " Healing the sick and casting out demons."},
{Question: "Q41: What is the shortest verse in the Bible?",	Answer: " John 11:35 Jesus wept."},
{Question: "Q42: Why did Jesus weep in that verse?",	Answer: " Because his friend Lazarus died."},
{Question: "Q43: How much bread and fish did Jesus use to feed more than 5,000 people?",	Answer: " Five loaves of bread—and two fish"},
{Question: "Q44: True or False: Jesus’ said washing hands is never important.",	Answer: "  False. He said dirty hands don’t make a person spiritually unclean. You can still get germs!"},
{Question: "Q45: True or False: Jesus asked the children to stay back while he was teaching important things to grown-ups.",	Answer: "  False–Jesus welcomed children."},
{Question: "Q46: What did Jesus do at the Last Supper to his disciples?",	Answer: " Washed their feet."},
{Question: "Q47: What did the woman pour on Jesus’ feet at the home of Simon the Leper?",	Answer: " Jar of expensive perfume"},
{Question: "Q48: Name the disciple who betrayed Jesus.",	Answer: " Judas Iscariot."},
{Question: "Q49: True or False: Jesus didn’t know that he was going to be arrested and killed in Jerusalem",	Answer: " False. He knew and told his disciples before it happened."},
{Question: "Q50: Which disciple denied Jesus three times?",	Answer: " Peter"},
{Question: "Q51: What happened after Jesus was buried in the tomb?",	Answer: " He rose again"},
{Question: "Q52: What was rolled away from the entrance of the tomb?",	Answer: " A large stone"},
{Question: "Q53: What day of the week did Jesus rise back to life?",	Answer: " Sunday"},
{Question: "Q54: How did Jesus leave Earth and go to Heaven?",	Answer: " He rose into the clouds."},
{Question: "Q55:  How many books have the name John in them?",	Answer: " Four."},
{Question: "Q56: Name the person who received the 10 Commandments from God?",	Answer: " Moses"},
{Question: "Q57: What is the 1st commandment?",	Answer: "  You shall have no other gods before me."},
{Question: "Q58: What is the 2nd commandment?",	Answer: " You shall not make idols."},
{Question: "Q59: What is the 3rd commandment?",	Answer: " You shall not misuse the name of the Lord."},
{Question: "Q60: What is the 4th commandment?",	Answer: " Observe the Sabbath day by keeping it holy."},
{Question: "Q61: What is the 5th commandment?",	Answer: " Honor your father and mother."},
{Question: "Q62: What is the 6th commandment?",	Answer: " You shall not murder."},
{Question: "Q63: What is the 7th commandment?",	Answer: " You shall not commit adultery."},
{Question: "Q64:  What is the 8th commandment?",	Answer: " You shall not steal."},
{Question: "Q65: What is the 9th commandment?",	Answer: " You shall not give false testimony."},
{Question: "Q66: What is the 10th commandment?",	Answer: " You shall not covet."},
{Question: "Q67: What does Jesus say is the first and greatest commandment?",	Answer: " Love God with all your heart, minds, soul, and strength."},
{Question: "Q68:  What does Jesus say is the second greatest commandment?",	Answer: " Love your neighbor as yourself."},
{Question: "Q69: What is the last book in the Bible?",	Answer: " Revelation"},
{Question: "Q70: What four books tell about Jesus' life on Earth?",	Answer: " Matthew, Mark, Luke, John"},
{Question: "Q71: Which book did Jesus directly write?",	Answer: " None"},
{Question: "Q72: Which book did David write most of?",	Answer: " Psalms"},
{Question: "Q73: True or False: The Bible was first written in the English language?",	Answer: " False"},
{Question: "Q74:  What were men trying to do at the Tower of Babel?",	Answer: " Build a tower to reach Heaven."},
{Question: "Q75: How did the 12 brothers get rid of Joseph?",	Answer: " Sold him to slave traders."},
{Question: "Q76: What did Joseph’s brothers tell their father had happened to him?",	Answer: " They said Joseph was killed by a wild animal"},
{Question: "Q77: Where did the slave traders take Joseph?",	Answer: " Egypt"},
{Question: "Q78: Who bought Joseph?",	Answer: " Potiphar, captain of the Pharaoh’s guards"},
{Question: "Q79: Who got Joseph thrown into prison by lying about him?",	Answer: "  Potiphar’s wife"},
{Question: "Q80: Who else was in prison with Joseph?",	Answer: " The Pharaoh’s cupbearer and chief baker."},
{Question: "Q81: What did Joseph do for them?",	Answer: " Interrupted their dreams."},
{Question: "Q82: Why was Joseph summoned out of prison by the Pharaoh?",	Answer: " To interrupt his dream."},
{Question: "Q83:  What position of power was Joseph given by the Pharaoh?",	Answer: " Second in command of Egypt."},
{Question: "Q84: What catastrophe did Joseph predict by interpreting the Pharaoh’s dream?",	Answer: " A severe, seven-year famine."},
{Question: "Q85: Who came to Egypt that Joseph recognized because of the famine?",	Answer: " His brothers"},
{Question: "Q86: What did Joseph tell the brothers to do next time they came back to Egypt?",	Answer: " To bring Benjamin back with them."},
{Question: "Q87: What was the giant’s name that David killed?",	Answer: " Goliath"},
{Question: "Q88: How did David kill Goliath?",	Answer: " A slingshot and a stone."},
{Question: "Q89: How many sling-throws did it take David to hit Goliath?",	Answer: " One."},
{Question: "Q90: When David wanted to fight Goliath, what did Saul try to give him?",	Answer: " His armour"},
{Question: "Q91: Who eventually came from the lineage of David?",	Answer: " Jesus"},
{Question: "Q92: True or False: Jesus was an only child.",	Answer: " False. Jesus had brothers and a sister."},
{Question: "Q93: How many of Jesus’ brothers are named in the Bible?",	Answer: " Four"},
{Question: "Q94: Is Jesus’s sister ever named in the Bible?",	Answer: " No."},
{Question: "Q95: Who was Jesus' most famous cousin?",	Answer: " John the Baptist."},
{Question: "Q96: Name one of Jesus’s brothers.",	Answer: " James, Joseph, Simon or Judas"},
{Question: "Q97: What happened when Jesus went into the wilderness?",	Answer: " He was tempted by Satan."},
{Question: "Q98:  How many people did Jesus feed with fish and bread?",	Answer: " 5,000"},
{Question: "Q99: How many lepers did Jesus heal?",	Answer: " 10"},
{ Question: "Q100: True or False: David wrote the entire book of Psalms.",	Answer: " False: The Psalms are a collection by many writers, but David contributed the most."},
{ Question: "Q101: What is the shortest book in the Bible?",	Answer: " 3 John."},
{ Question: "Q102: How many books are in the Bible?",	Answer: " 66."},
{ Question: "Q103: How many books in the Old Testament?",	Answer: " 39."},
{ Question: "Q104: How many books in the New Testament?",	Answer: " 27."},
{ Question: "Q105:  Which New Testament book has Jesus' Sermon on the Mount?",	Answer: " Matthew"},
{ Question: "Q106: Who was David’s son that became king?",	Answer: " Solomon."},
{ Question: "Q107:  In what language was most of the Old Testament given?",	Answer: " Hebrew."},
{ Question: "Q108:  In what language was most of the New Testament given?",	Answer: " Greek."},
{ Question: "Q109:  Which human author wrote the most books?",	Answer: " Paul wrote 13 books."},
{ Question: "Q110:  Which human author wrote the most words in the Bible?",	Answer: " Moses wrote 125,139 words."},
{ Question: "Q111:  What was most likely the first Gospel written?",	Answer: " Mark."},
{ Question: "Q112:  What was most likely the last Gospel written?",	Answer: "John"},
{ Question: "Q113:  What was most likely the first of Paul's letters written?",	Answer: " 1 Thessalonians."},
{ Question: "Q114:   What was most likely the last New Testament book written?",	Answer: " Revelation."},
{ Question: "Q115:  Who were Noah’s three sons?",	Answer: "  Shem, Ham, Japheth."},
{ Question: "Q116:  How many people were saved on the ark?",	Answer: " 8"},
{ Question: "Q117:   How did God make people spread out across the earth?",	Answer: " Confused their languages."},
{ Question: "Q118:  Who did God call out of Ur to move to Canaan?",	Answer: " Abram."},
{ Question: "Q119:  Who was Abram’s wife?",	Answer: " Sarai."},
{ Question: "Q120:  Even though Abram and Sarah were too old, what did God promise them?",	Answer: " A son."},
{ Question: "Q121:  When God showed Abram the stars in the sky, what did he promise?",	Answer: " That Abram would have more descendants than the number of stars."},
{ Question: "Q122: : Who was Abram’s handmaid?",	Answer: " Hagar."},
{ Question: "Q123:  What was Sarai’s idea for Abram to have a child?",	Answer: " For Abram to have a child with Hagar."},
{ Question: "Q124:  Who was the first son Abram had?",	Answer: " Ishmael."},
{ Question: "Q125:  What was Abram’s name changed to?",	Answer: " Abraham."},
{ Question: "Q126:  What was Sarai’s name changed to?",	Answer: " Sarah."},
{ Question: "Q127:  What was the second son Abraham had?",	Answer: " Issac."},
{ Question: "Q128:   Who did Abraham have his second son with?",	Answer: " Sarah."},
{ Question: "Q129:  Where did Hagar and her son go after they left Abraham’s?",	Answer: " Into the desert."},
{ Question: "Q130:   Who did Abraham send to find Isaac a wife?",	Answer: " His oldest servant."},
{ Question: "Q131:  Who did the servant choose?",	Answer: " Rebekah."},
{ Question: "Q132:  What were Isaac’s sons’ names?",	Answer: " Jacob and Esau"},
{ Question: "Q133:  Who was born first?",	Answer: " Esau came first, with Jacob grabbing his heel."},
{ Question: "Q134:  How did Esau provide food for the family?",	Answer: " He hunted"},
{ Question: "Q135:  Who did Isaac favor of his two sons?",	Answer: " Esau"},
{ Question: "Q136:  What did Jacob do most of the time?",	Answer: " Stay at home with his mother."},
{ Question: "Q137:  What did Esau receive in exchange for his birthright?",	Answer: " Stew"},
{ Question: "Q138:  As Isaac was dying and blind, who suggested that Jacob should steal Esau’s birthright?",	Answer: " Rebekah."},
{ Question: "Q139:   How did Esau respond when his birthright was taken?",	Answer: " Threatened to kill Jacob."},
{ Question: "Q140:  When Jacob met Laban, which daughter did he want to marry?",	Answer: " Rachel."},
{ Question: "Q141:  Who did Laban trick Jacob into marrying?",	Answer: " Leah."},
{ Question: "Q142:  What did Laban make Jacob do to finally marry Rachel?",	Answer: " Work another 7 years."},
{ Question: "Q143:   Who was the first son Jacob had with Rachel?",	Answer: " Joseph."},
{ Question: "Q144:  What did God change Jacob’s name to before his meeting with Esau?",	Answer: " Israel."},
{ Question: "Q145:  What did Moses do after he killed an Egyptian?",	Answer: " Fled into the desert."},
{ Question: "Q146:   When Moses confronted the Pharaoh, what did his staff turn into when he threw it on the ground?",	Answer: " A snake"},
{ Question: "Q147:  How did Moses’ mother save him from the Egyptian soldiers?",	Answer: " Put him in a basket in the river."},
{ Question: "Q148:  What did God send to feed the Israelites in the desert?",	Answer: " Quail and manna."},
{ Question: "Q149:  What did the spies sent into Canaan see that made them scared?",	Answer: " Giants in the land."},
{ Question: "Q150:   Who were the only two Israelites allowed to go into the Promised Land after many years?",	Answer: "  Joshua and Caleb"},
{ Question: "Q151:   What city did God make the walls fall so Joshua and the Israelites could conquer it?",	Answer: " Jericho."},
{ Question: "Q152:  After they took over the Promised Land and Joshua died, who ruled Israel?",	Answer: " Judges."},
{ Question: "Q153:  Who was the woman judge who led Israel to victory?",	Answer: " Deborah."},
{ Question: "Q154:   Who was the judge who defeated the Midianites with only 300 men using torches and horns?",	Answer: " Gideon."},
{ Question: "Q155:  Who was the judge who took a Nazarite vow from birth and fought against the Philistines?",	Answer: " Samson"},
{ Question: "Q156:  With what did Samson kill 1,000 Philistines?",	Answer: " A donkey’s jawbone."},
{ Question: "Q157:  How did Samson die?",	Answer: " Pushing over the temple pillars, killing himself and many Philistines."},
{ Question: "Q158:  Who anointed Saul as King?",	Answer: " Samuel."},
{ Question: "Q159:  Who was the enemy who took the Ark of the Covenant?",	Answer: " Philistines."},
{ Question: "Q160:  What happened to the idol which was beside the Ark in the enemy’s temple?",	Answer: " It fell over and broke."},
{ Question: "Q161:  When the people demanded Saul make a sacrifice to God, what did he do?",	Answer: " Made the sacrifice."},
{ Question: "Q162:   What was Saul’s punishment for disobeying?",	Answer: ": God took away his kingdom."},
{ Question: "Q163:  Who was the king of Israel anointed by Samuel after Saul?",	Answer: " David."},
{ Question: "Q164:  What did David do as a job as he worked for his father?",	Answer: " He was a shepherd."},
{ Question: "Q165:   When the Philistines came to attack the Israelites, who mocked God and challenged them?",	Answer: " Goliath the Giant."},
{ Question: "Q166:  Who was Saul’s son that David befriended?",	Answer: " Jonathan."},
{ Question: "Q167:  What did Saul throw to try to kill David?",	Answer: " A spear."},
{ Question: "Q168:  What did Jonathan do to save David’s life from Saul?",	Answer: ": Warned him that Saul would try to kill him."},
{ Question: "Q169:   What foreign country did David run away to?",	Answer: ": The Land of the Philistines."},
{ Question: "Q170:  Did Saul give up on chasing David when David went into the wilderness?",	Answer: " No."},
{ Question: "Q171:  How many times did David spare Saul’s life?",	Answer: ": Twice."},
{ Question: "Q172:  Where did David spare Saul’s life the first time?",	Answer: " A cave."},
{ Question: "Q173:   Where did David spare Saul’s life the second time?",	Answer: " In a campsite, where Saul was sleeping."},
{ Question: "Q174:  What last judge of Israel died after Saul made a temporary peace with David?",	Answer: " Samuel."},
{ Question: "Q175:  What prophet did Saul ask to speak to?",	Answer: " Samuel."},
{ Question: "Q176:  How did Saul die?",	Answer: " Fell on his own sword."},
{ Question: "Q177:   How many of his sons died in battle?",	Answer: " All of them."},
{ Question: "Q178:   Who was David’s captain of his army?",	Answer: " Joab."},
{ Question: "Q179:  When David stayed in Jerusalem, what woman did he see and commit adultery with?",	Answer: " Bathsheba."},
{ Question: "Q180:  Who was Bathsheba’s husband?",	Answer: " Uriah."},
{ Question: "Q181:  When Bathsheba got pregnant, what did David make happen to Uriah?",	Answer: " Have him killed in battle."},
{ Question: "Q182:  What prophet came to rebuke David?",	Answer: " Nathan."},
{ Question: "Q183:  What happened to Bathsheba’s child?",	Answer: " The child died."},
{ Question: "Q184:  When Bathsheba and David had another child, what did they name him?",	Answer: " Solomon."},
{ Question: "Q185:  Who was David’s son that started a rebellion against him?",	Answer: " Absalom."},
{ Question: "Q186:  What capital city did David abandon?",	Answer: " Jerusalem."},
{ Question: "Q187:  When David and Absalom’s armies battled, what happened to Absalom’s hair?",	Answer: ": It got caught in a tree."},
{ Question: "Q188:  Who killed Absalom?",	Answer: " Joab."},
{ Question: "Q189:   Because he killed Absalom, what was Joab’s punishment?",	Answer: " He got demoted as captain."},
{ Question: "Q190:  What was David’s second sin recorded in the Bible?",	Answer: " He took a census of the people in his nation."},
{ Question: "Q191:  Which books of the Bible record David’s time as king?",	Answer: " 1st and 2nd Samuel"},
{ Question: "Q192:   During his time as king, who was David’s main enemy?",	Answer: " Philistines."},
{ Question: "Q193:  What trait did Solomon pray for from God when he became king?",	Answer: " Wisdom"},
{ Question: "Q194:  What did Solomon build for the Lord?",	Answer: " A temple."},
{ Question: "Q195:  What famous queen came to visit Solomon?",	Answer: " Queen of Sheba."},
{ Question: "Q196:  How many wives did Solomon have?",	Answer: " 700."},
{ Question: "Q197:  Did Solomon always follow the Lord?",	Answer: " No. He turned away from God."},
{ Question: "Q198:  Who convinced Solomon to turn from God?",	Answer: " His wives."},
{ Question: "Q199:   What happened to the kingdom after Solomon’s rule?",	Answer: " It split into two."},

];

const NewBibleToo = [
{ Question: "Q1:  True or False: David wrote the entire book of Psalms.",	Answer: " False: The Psalms are a collection by many writers, but David contributed the most."},
{ Question: "Q2:  What is the shortest book in the Bible?",	Answer: " 3 John."},
{ Question: "Q3:  How many books are in the Bible?",	Answer: " 66."},
{ Question: "Q4:  How many books in the Old Testament?",	Answer: " 39."},
{ Question: "Q5:  How many books in the New Testament?",	Answer: " 27."},
{ Question: "Q6:   Which New Testament book has Jesus' Sermon on the Mount?",	Answer: " Matthew"},
{ Question: "Q7:  Who was David’s son that became king?",	Answer: " Solomon."},
{ Question: "Q8:   In what language was most of the Old Testament given?",	Answer: " Hebrew."},
{ Question: "Q9:   In what language was most of the New Testament given?",	Answer: " Greek."},
{ Question: "Q10:  Which human author wrote the most books?",	Answer: " Paul wrote 13 books."},
{ Question: "Q11:  Which human author wrote the most words in the Bible?",	Answer: " Moses wrote 125,139 words."},
{ Question: "Q12:  What was most likely the first Gospel written?",	Answer: " Mark."},
{ Question: "Q13:  What was most likely the last Gospel written?",	Answer: "John"},
{ Question: "Q14:  What was most likely the first of Paul's letters written?",	Answer: " 1 Thessalonians."},
{ Question: "Q15:   What was most likely the last New Testament book written?",	Answer: " Revelation."},
{ Question: "Q16:  Who were Noah’s three sons?",	Answer: "  Shem, Ham, Japheth."},
{ Question: "Q17:  How many people were saved on the ark?",	Answer: " 8"},
{ Question: "Q18:   How did God make people spread out across the earth?",	Answer: " Confused their languages."},
{ Question: "Q19:  Who did God call out of Ur to move to Canaan?",	Answer: " Abram."},
{ Question: "Q20:  Who was Abram’s wife?",	Answer: " Sarai."},
{ Question: "Q21:  Even though Abram and Sarah were too old, what did God promise them?",	Answer: " A son."},
{ Question: "Q22:  When God showed Abram the stars in the sky, what did he promise?",	Answer: " That Abram would have more descendants than the number of stars."},
{ Question: "Q23: : Who was Abram’s handmaid?",	Answer: " Hagar."},
{ Question: "Q24:  What was Sarai’s idea for Abram to have a child?",	Answer: " For Abram to have a child with Hagar."},
{ Question: "Q25:  Who was the first son Abram had?",	Answer: " Ishmael."},
{ Question: "Q26:  What was Abram’s name changed to?",	Answer: " Abraham."},
{ Question: "Q27:  What was Sarai’s name changed to?",	Answer: " Sarah."},
{ Question: "Q28:  What was the second son Abraham had?",	Answer: " Issac."},
{ Question: "Q29:   Who did Abraham have his second son with?",	Answer: " Sarah."},
{ Question: "Q30:  Where did Hagar and her son go after they left Abraham’s?",	Answer: " Into the desert."},
{ Question: "Q31:   Who did Abraham send to find Isaac a wife?",	Answer: " His oldest servant."},
{ Question: "Q32:  Who did the servant choose?",	Answer: " Rebekah."},
{ Question: "Q33:  What were Isaac’s sons’ names?",	Answer: " Jacob and Esau"},
{ Question: "Q34:  Who was born first?",	Answer: " Esau came first, with Jacob grabbing his heel."},
{ Question: "Q35:  How did Esau provide food for the family?",	Answer: " He hunted"},
{ Question: "Q36:  Who did Isaac favor of his two sons?",	Answer: " Esau"},
{ Question: "Q37:  What did Jacob do most of the time?",	Answer: " Stay at home with his mother."},
{ Question: "Q38:  What did Esau receive in exchange for his birthright?",	Answer: " Stew"},
{ Question: "Q39:  As Isaac was dying and blind, who suggested that Jacob should steal Esau’s birthright?",	Answer: " Rebekah."},
{ Question: "Q40:   How did Esau respond when his birthright was taken?",	Answer: " Threatened to kill Jacob."},
{ Question: "Q41:  When Jacob met Laban, which daughter did he want to marry?",	Answer: " Rachel."},
{ Question: "Q42:  Who did Laban trick Jacob into marrying?",	Answer: " Leah."},
{ Question: "Q43:  What did Laban make Jacob do to finally marry Rachel?",	Answer: " Work another 7 years."},
{ Question: "Q44:   Who was the first son Jacob had with Rachel?",	Answer: " Joseph."},
{ Question: "Q45:  What did God change Jacob’s name to before his meeting with Esau?",	Answer: " Israel."},
{ Question: "Q46:  What did Moses do after he killed an Egyptian?",	Answer: " Fled into the desert."},
{ Question: "Q47:   When Moses confronted the Pharaoh, what did his staff turn into when he threw it on the ground?",	Answer: " A snake"},
{ Question: "Q48:  How did Moses’ mother save him from the Egyptian soldiers?",	Answer: " Put him in a basket in the river."},
{ Question: "Q49:  What did God send to feed the Israelites in the desert?",	Answer: " Quail and manna."},
{ Question: "Q50:  What did the spies sent into Canaan see that made them scared?",	Answer: " Giants in the land."},
{ Question: "Q51:   Who were the only two Israelites allowed to go into the Promised Land after many years?",	Answer: "  Joshua and Caleb"},
{ Question: "Q52:   What city did God make the walls fall so Joshua and the Israelites could conquer it?",	Answer: " Jericho."},
{ Question: "Q53:  After they took over the Promised Land and Joshua died, who ruled Israel?",	Answer: " Judges."},
{ Question: "Q54:  Who was the woman judge who led Israel to victory?",	Answer: " Deborah."},
{ Question: "Q55:   Who was the judge who defeated the Midianites with only 300 men using torches and horns?",	Answer: " Gideon."},
{ Question: "Q56:  Who was the judge who took a Nazarite vow from birth and fought against the Philistines?",	Answer: " Samson"},
{ Question: "Q57:  With what did Samson kill 1,000 Philistines?",	Answer: " A donkey’s jawbone."},
{ Question: "Q58:  How did Samson die?",	Answer: " Pushing over the temple pillars, killing himself and many Philistines."},
{ Question: "Q59:  Who anointed Saul as King?",	Answer: " Samuel."},
{ Question: "Q60:  Who was the enemy who took the Ark of the Covenant?",	Answer: " Philistines."},
{ Question: "Q61:  What happened to the idol which was beside the Ark in the enemy’s temple?",	Answer: " It fell over and broke."},
{ Question: "Q62:  When the people demanded Saul make a sacrifice to God, what did he do?",	Answer: " Made the sacrifice."},
{ Question: "Q63:   What was Saul’s punishment for disobeying?",	Answer: ": God took away his kingdom."},
{ Question: "Q64:  Who was the king of Israel anointed by Samuel after Saul?",	Answer: " David."},
{ Question: "Q65:  What did David do as a job as he worked for his father?",	Answer: " He was a shepherd."},
{ Question: "Q66:   When the Philistines came to attack the Israelites, who mocked God and challenged them?",	Answer: " Goliath the Giant."},
{ Question: "Q67:  Who was Saul’s son that David befriended?",	Answer: " Jonathan."},
{ Question: "Q68:  What did Saul throw to try to kill David?",	Answer: " A spear."},
{ Question: "Q69:  What did Jonathan do to save David’s life from Saul?",	Answer: ": Warned him that Saul would try to kill him."},
{ Question: "Q70:   What foreign country did David run away to?",	Answer: ": The Land of the Philistines."},
{ Question: "Q71:  Did Saul give up on chasing David when David went into the wilderness?",	Answer: " No."},
{ Question: "Q72:  How many times did David spare Saul’s life?",	Answer: ": Twice."},
{ Question: "Q73:  Where did David spare Saul’s life the first time?",	Answer: " A cave."},
{ Question: "Q74:   Where did David spare Saul’s life the second time?",	Answer: " In a campsite, where Saul was sleeping."},
{ Question: "Q75:  What last judge of Israel died after Saul made a temporary peace with David?",	Answer: " Samuel."},
{ Question: "Q76:  What prophet did Saul ask to speak to?",	Answer: " Samuel."},
{ Question: "Q77:  How did Saul die?",	Answer: " Fell on his own sword."},
{ Question: "Q78:   How many of his sons died in battle?",	Answer: " All of them."},
{ Question: "Q79:   Who was David’s captain of his army?",	Answer: " Joab."},
{ Question: "Q80:  When David stayed in Jerusalem, what woman did he see and commit adultery with?",	Answer: " Bathsheba."},
{ Question: "Q81:  Who was Bathsheba’s husband?",	Answer: " Uriah."},
{ Question: "Q82:  When Bathsheba got pregnant, what did David make happen to Uriah?",	Answer: " Have him killed in battle."},
{ Question: "Q83:  What prophet came to rebuke David?",	Answer: " Nathan."},
{ Question: "Q84:  What happened to Bathsheba’s child?",	Answer: " The child died."},
{ Question: "Q85:  When Bathsheba and David had another child, what did they name him?",	Answer: " Solomon."},
{ Question: "Q86:  Who was David’s son that started a rebellion against him?",	Answer: " Absalom."},
{ Question: "Q87:  What capital city did David abandon?",	Answer: " Jerusalem."},
{ Question: "Q88:  When David and Absalom’s armies battled, what happened to Absalom’s hair?",	Answer: ": It got caught in a tree."},
{ Question: "Q89:  Who killed Absalom?",	Answer: " Joab."},
{ Question: "Q90:   Because he killed Absalom, what was Joab’s punishment?",	Answer: " He got demoted as captain."},
{ Question: "Q91:  What was David’s second sin recorded in the Bible?",	Answer: " He took a census of the people in his nation."},
{ Question: "Q92:  Which books of the Bible record David’s time as king?",	Answer: " 1st and 2nd Samuel"},
{ Question: "Q93:   During his time as king, who was David’s main enemy?",	Answer: " Philistines."},
{ Question: "Q94:  What trait did Solomon pray for from God when he became king?",	Answer: " Wisdom"},
{ Question: "Q95:  What did Solomon build for the Lord?",	Answer: " A temple."},
{ Question: "Q96:  What famous queen came to visit Solomon?",	Answer: " Queen of Sheba."},
{ Question: "Q97:  How many wives did Solomon have?",	Answer: " 700."},
{ Question: "Q98:  Did Solomon always follow the Lord?",	Answer: " No. He turned away from God."},
{ Question: "Q99:  Who convinced Solomon to turn from God?",	Answer: " His wives."},
{ Question: "Q100:  What happened to the kingdom after Solomon’s rule?",	Answer: " It split into two."},
];

